(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T04:27:11.520736",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
またねよ
See you later.
にっこり
Smiling.
あらあら
My, my.
眠い
Sleepy...
そこも眠い
Sleepy there too.
いっちょこ
Itchoko.
待って待って待って待って
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
こっち
Over here.
どうも！ホロライブ2期生悪魔の癒月ちょこです
Hello! I'm Yuzuki Choco, devil of Hololive 2nd Gen!
おべん何1つじゃあ
What kind of lunchbox...
うわあ！
Whoa!
テキサスパチャン？ テキサスベルマッチ？ ほら、豚、のぼって、がんばって、豚、ほら、豚、こっちよこっち、どっち？
Come on, pig, climb up, do your best, pig! Over here, pig, which one?
はいはいはいはい
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
なんね、何ねやってると思ってるんですか？ ええ？
What on earth do you think you're doing? Huh?
先生に向かってなんですかその言葉遣いは。友達じゃないんですよ。いいですか？
What kind of language is that toward your teacher? I'm not your friend, you know. Okay?
癒月ちょこ先生だからね！
Because I'm Yuzuki Choco-sensei!
おやばい！
Oh, yabai!
うわあ！
Whoa!
美味しかったの
It was delicious...
あ、違う！
Ah, wait, no!
だめ！
Don't!
ちょこしかおらん
Only Choco is here.
バカ！ごいた！
Idiot! ...
まだアイス！
Still ice cream!
はい、いらっしゃいませ
Hello, welcome.
どこ行きせいねよ？行きせい！なー
Where are you going? Iki-sei! Naー
おやすみー
Good nightー
あー、いい天気！
Ah, what nice weather!
保健室のベッドでお昼寝したい！
I want to take a nap in the nurse's office bed!
すぐ休み。許されない？
Taking a break right away. Is that not allowed?
保健室は人生なのさ
The nurse's office is my life!
サボってる？ちょ、待たせて！
Slacking off? Wait, make them wait!
誰も来なきゃやる気でない！
If nobody comes, I have no motivation!
ちょこちょこせーしょん！イエイ！
Choco Choco Sensation! Yay!
ちょこちょこせーしょん！
Choco Choco Sensation!
このままであたし駄目みたい
Looks like I'm no good staying like this.
はあ、大きなキャットタワー宝箱2回目の欠伸をお休みなさい
Ah, big cat tower, treasure box, second yawn, go get some rest!
ごめんなさい！ちょっとだけ寝かせて先生もうちょっとだもん！
I'm sorry! Let me sleep just a little longer, sensei, just a bit more!
夢見るふわふわずっとこうして眠りたい
Dreaming, fluffy, I want to sleep like this forever.
ありがと！ぽかぽかちょっとすずけしてるだけ！
Thank you! Warm and cozy, just chilling for a bit!
自由だんだん的ね
So increasingly free-spirited.
急に筋肉痛来るなんて、ねえ？どこか悪いの？
Suddenly getting muscle pain, huh? Is something wrong somewhere?
何かお祈りしているのかなあ？
I wonder if you're praying for something?
揺らう心めぐる感情、口づけ交わすせいせーしょん！
Wavering hearts, revolving emotions, an affectionate session exchanging kisses!
癒されたい甘えていたいよ！手をちょこせーしょん！
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled! Give me a Choco Sensation!
君の視線君の対応わかっても恋は測れない
Your gaze, your reaction—even if I understand, love cannot be measured.
元気なのにため息しちゃうの、すこしって何かこの病気
Full of energy yet sighing—just a bit, what is this strange illness?
点滴ドキドキするまで動けないから、時計見て運んでってまいきゅーでず
I can't move until the IV makes my heart race, so look at the clock and bring it over, my Q-death!
自由休み、また来たの？
A free day off, you came again?
保健室は人生なのさ
The nurse's office is my life!
サボってた？ちょ、待たせて！
Were you slacking off? Wait, make them wait!
やっぱり君に引いてほしい
After all, I want you to pull me in.
明日は週末お休み
Tomorrow is a weekend holiday.
なんだよ！家のみ！最高！
What is this! Drinking at home! The best!
引きこもり最高！
Shut-in life is the best!
持ちだすノーメイク、着飾るようになったら白衣脱ぎます
If I start dressing up without makeup, I'll take off my lab coat.
さあすべてを見せて、完璧なんてないじゃん？
Now show me everything, perfection doesn't exist, right?
何を隠してるの？鼓動のスピードは聞こえてるよ
What are you hiding? I can hear the speed of your heartbeat.
見せて心めぐるシャツを正常保てる点滴ーそう！
Show me, revolving shirts, keeping a normal IV—that's right!
愛されたい頼られたい甘えていたいよ！手をちょこせーしょん！
I want to be loved, relied on, and spoiled! Give me a Choco Sensation!
君の重み君の匂いわかっても愛は測れない
Your weight, your scent—even if I understand, love cannot be measured.
大好きだからため息しちゃうよやっぱりそれは恋の病気
Because I love you so much, I sigh—after all, that's love sickness.
点滴ドキドキするまで動けないから、時計見て運んでってまいきゅーでず
I can't move until the IV makes my heart race, so look at the clock and bring it over, my Q-death!
馬鹿言いたって、この世界だって、みんな癒やしが必要だから！
Talking nonsense, in this world too, everyone needs healing!
ちょこちょこせーしょん！イエイ！ちょこちょこせーしょん！イエイ！
Choco Choco Sensation! Yay! Choco Choco Sensation! Yay!
ちょこちょこせーしょん！イエイ！絶対君もダメにしたい！
Choco Choco Sensation! Yay! I definitely want to make you useless too!
ちょこちょこせーしょん！
Choco Choco Sensation!
ゆらぐ心めぐる感情 くちどけ甘い sensation
A wavering heart, spinning emotions, a meltingly sweet sensation.
癒されたい 甘えていたい だよておちょこ sensation
I want to be healed, I want to be spoiled, Choco's sensation.
君の視点 君の対応 分かっても恋は測れない
Your perspective, your response... Even if I understand, I can't measure love.
元気なのにため息しちゃう もしかしてもて遅れ
Sighing even though I'm fine... Could it be arriving too late?
でもどちどちするまで動けないからときめき運んできて毎週で
But I can't move until my heart pounds, so bring me excitement every week!
ちょこちょこ sensation Yay!
Choco Choco Sensation, Yay!
絶対君もダメにしたい
I definitely want to ruin you too!
はーい、ということで！
So, um...
癒月ちょこ生誕祭2026、始まりましたー！
Yuzuki Choco's Birthday Celebration 2026 has begun!
見てみて！一曲目からちょこ、
Look, look! Right from the first song,
生まれ変わりましたー！
Choco has been reborn!
いや今日はね、原点回帰ということで、
Today, as a return to our roots,
ちょこのなんと、保健室ステージなのー！
It's Choco's nurse's office stage!
保健室もちょっと生まれ変わって、めちゃめちゃ可愛くなりましたー！
The nurse's office has been reborn and is super cute!
少女漫画ドラマとかできそうよねー！
You could totally make a shojo manga drama out of this!
今日は生まれ変わった新ちょこと、素敵なね、ゲスト様をいっぱい呼んで
Today, with the reborn new Choco and lots of wonderful guests,
ライブをしていくんだけど、
we'll be doing a live show, but...
その前に！みんなちょことのこともっと見たいよね！
Before that! Everyone wants to see more of Choco, right?
あ、でも、まだダメだよ？
Ah, but it's not time yet!
これから来るお二人に、ちょこの撮影会をご依頼しちゃいましたー！
I've requested a photoshoot with the two guests arriving soon!
それでは早速呼んでいきましょう！
Now then, let's call them out right away!
ノエル様！ラミィ様！
Noel-sama! Lamy-sama!
ちょこせん、せーの、ちょこ先生、お誕生日おめでとー！
Choco-sen— ready, set— Choco-sensei, happy birthday!
ありがとうございまーす！うれしー！
Thank you so much! Yay!
そういうことで、今回はね、この可愛い両手に花で、
So, this time, surrounded by two lovely flowers,
可愛いお二人と一緒に撮影会をしてもらおうと思うんだけど、まずは自己紹介よろしくお願いします！のいちゃんから！
we'll be doing a photoshoot! First, please introduce yourselves, starting with Noel-chan!
はい、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと！
Hi, I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Generation,
はい、ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！
and Yukihana Lamy from Hololive 5th Generation!
今日はよろしくお願いします！
We're looking forward to today!
まあね、ちょっとちょこ先生の本当に可愛くなったところ、ちょっと団長頑張って攻めていこうと思いますのでよろしくお願いします！
Well, Choco-sensei got so cute, so I'll do my best as Danchou to push forward!
ぜひぜひ！ラミィもギリギリを攻めていきたいと思います！
Definitely! Lamy wants to push the limits too!
いや、撮影会やるならちょっとね、この二人を呼ぶしかないかなって思って、呼んじゃいました！
I figured if I was doing a photoshoot, I just had to invite these two, so I called them!
うれしー！かもしかも！
We're so happy! Plus, plus!
この3人から、なんと、お知らせもあるみたいなので！
It seems the three of us have an announcement to make as well!
お知らせなんだろー！気になるー！
What could the announcement be? I'm curious!
まあ、撮影会のあとで、皆様、楽しみに待っててくださーい！
Well, everyone look forward to it after the photoshoot!
それじゃあちょこちょ、こちらで撮影会よろしくお願いします！
Now then, Choco-cho, please lead us to the photoshoot here!
わ、なんかすごいとこ来たぞ！すごーい！
Whoa, we came somewhere amazing! Amazing!
かわいいー！かわいいでしょ！
So cute! Isn't it cute?
撮影会は、ちょこここの、新診察室でやりますー！新診察室だー！ちょこ先生の新診察室ー！すげーかわいい！
We'll do the photoshoot in Choco's new examination room! It's the new examination room! So cute!
いいでしょ、いいでしょ。
Isn't this nice? Isn't this nice?
え、でもさ、診察室だけど、
Wait, but this is an examination room,
べ、べ、ベッドは？ベッドどこ？
wh-wh-where's the bed? Where is it?
ベッドどこ？あ、うん。
Where's the bed? Ah, yeah.
え、なんかパネルもあれなんだけど あれ使う？
Wait, and what about that panel? Should we use that?
ああ、ちょっとそこは、パネルパネルってなるのがあるけど、え、これ駄目なの？
Ah, wait, there's that panel thing... Wait, is this no good?
そこは、後のメンテナンスで使うの？
Do we use that for maintenance later?
え？なに？そうなんだ！メンテナンス！
Huh? What? That's right! Maintenance!
ちょっとね、ベッドとか、ちょっと色々撮影会とか シチュエーションドラマとかやろうかなって
I was thinking of doing things like a bed, photo shoots, and situation dramas.
シチュエーションドラマ？
Situation dramas?
とんでもないことをしようとしてる！
You're trying to do something outrageous!
やそうなんですようー。
That's right, yeah~.
ま、ね、それは置いといて、ちょっと今回は、
Well, anyway, putting that aside, this time,
2人に撮影をしてもらいたいので、まずは、
I want the two of you to do a photo shoot, so first,
撮りますよ。
we'll take them.
ラミィ様には、
For Lamy-sama,
おっ？
Oh?
え、本格的な！すごい、カメラ来たー！
Wh-What a professional one! Wow, a camera's here!
そして、ノエル様にはこちらの、じゃじゃーん！
And for Noel-sama, we have this, ta-da!
何だいこれ？
What is this?
チョコのジリジリを守るために特別に作られたモザイク棒です！
It's a special mosaic stick made to protect Choco's private bits!
モザイク、ボタンでこのモザイクの荒さを変えられるらしい！
With the mosaic button, you can change the coarseness of the mosaic!
今めっちゃ荒くなってるから、
Right now it's super coarse, so,
あ、ほんと薄くできる！
oh, you can really make it thin!
ほんとだ！
Really!
すげえ！でも荒い方がむしろいいまであるな、これ。
Amazing! But having it coarser is actually even better.
確かに。オッケー、隠すやん。
True. Okay, it hides it.
これ大丈夫かな。でも配信、ちょっと、チョコの配信を、守ってくださる。
Is this okay? But please protect Choco's stream.
頑張ります！頑張ります！
We'll do our best! We'll do our best!
それでは、撮影会、スタート！
And now, the photo shoot starts!
やったー！
Yay!
まずはやっぱり全身。
First, of course, the full body.
そうだね。普通にこうね、ちょっとポーズ、いつものチョコ線の、
That's right. Normally like this, a pose, Choco-sen's usual...
こんな感じ？美しいコップ、美しい！
Like this? Beautiful cup, beautiful!
あー、いいね、いいね。え、可愛い！
Ah, nice, nice. Eh, cute!
もう、ここちょっとまずいんじゃないの、ここ。まずいかなあ。
Wait, isn't this part a bit bad? Is it bad?
なんか逆に、え、逆にちょっと、
Wait, conversely... wait, conversely, a bit...
ノリノリなんですけど。
We're getting really into it.
まずいかなあ。ちょっとここ揺れ、モザイクだ、モザイクの追いつきが不い
Is it bad? Wait, this is shaking... Mosaic, it can't keep up with the mosaic!
じゃ、ノエル様頑張って、頑張って！
Now Noel-sama, do your best, do your best!
えい！こうやってね、あ、こういう感じでね。で、ちょっと、あ、どんどん、
Like this, right? Ah, like this. And then, it keeps going...
ちょっとジャンプしてもらってみてもらっても、
Try jumping for us and let us see.
あ、ジャンプ、確かに。すごいブルル、
Ah, jumping, true. It jiggles so much—
あ、やばい、やばい、やばい！駄目んでしょ、これ！
Ah, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous! This is no good!
あらー。
Oh my.
え、ちょっとせっかくだから、椅子とかももう座っちゃう？
Eh, since we're at it, should we sit on the chair too?
あ、椅子ね、ここにあるね。ありますね。ふう。よいしょ、いたっ。
Ah, the chair, it's here. There is one. Whew. Yoisho, ouch.
靴も可愛い！
Even the shoes are cute!
なんかちょっと青っぽいんだね。
It looks kind of bluish, huh.
あ、そう、チョコね、そこが赤なの。えー！
Ah, right, Choco's, that part is red. Eh?!
あ、まずいありがとうございます。
Ah, wait, thank you very much.
そこがね、赤なのこれ。ありがとうございます。
That part is red, you see. Thank you very much.
大丈夫、あ、でもなんも見えてないからね。
It's fine, ah, but nothing is visible, so.
大丈夫です、大丈夫です、セーフですね。チャンネル守ってます！チャンネル守ってます！
It's fine, it's fine, it's safe. We're protecting the channel! We're protecting the channel!
いい、じゃあこうどんどん、上を、うん、見てもらって、
Alright, then like this, keep looking up...
あ、いいね！
Ah, nice!
あら、可愛い！
Aww, cute!
見えてる？見えてるよ、見えてるよ！見えてるう！
Can you see? I can see, I can see! I can see it~!
え、ちなみにラミィさん、
Eh, by the way Lamy-san,
可愛い子
(Cute voice)
あれですよ、この椅子に座って先生ポーズも、気持ちよくなってけど、
You know, sitting on this chair and doing the teacher pose feels good, but—
先生ポーズ撮ってほしい！
I want you to take a teacher pose!
こんな感じ？
Like this?
あー、いいですねー！非常に良い！
Ah, nice! Very good!
モザイクいらないね、これは。
We don't need a mosaic for this.
非常に、本当にいらないのかこれ？
Very much... do we really not need it?
いや分かんない、わかんない、チョコ線の魅力が溢れすぎてて、
I don't know, I don't know, Choco-sen's charm is overflowing,
いいですね。
it's nice.
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
え、じゃあ、団長もいいですか？
Eh, then Danchou, is it okay?
お、なに？なに？おしりふりふり、ちょっと、していただきたいんで、ちょっと、ふりふり。
Oh, what? What? I want you to shake your hips a bit, shake shake.
ええと、そう、後ろ向いてもらって、で、
Um, right, turn around to the back, and—
背中越しだけど、ふりふり。あ、いいね！背中越しだが！
Over the shoulder, shake shake. Ah, nice! Even over the shoulder!
その下に、その、あ、ちょっと、その下にスカート結構きわどい。これ、かくっ、て、これ、脱げ、脱いでほしいんだけど、これ脱げないの？
Under that, that, ah, wait, under that the skirt is quite daring. Can you take this off? Can't you take it off?
脱げるけど、メンテナンスでって言ってた。
You can take it off, but you said 'for maintenance'.
あ！メンテナンスなら脱いでくれるんですね！
Ah! If it's maintenance, you'll take it off!
え、ガニ股は、あのチョコ会長リスペクトで、団長ガニ股好きなんで、
Eh, the sumo stance is in respect to Choco chairman, Danchou likes sumo stances, so—
ガニ股！
Sumo stance!
ガニ股最高！
Sumo stance is the best!
ガニ股最高！ガニ股助かる！
Sumo stance is the best! Sumo stance is a lifesaver!
ガニ股だ！
Sumo stance!
これ、ちょっとモザイク、モザイク！
This, wait, mosaic, mosaic!
ちょっと見えてるもん、な！モザイクお願いします！
It's showing, right! Mosaic please!
モザイクがもう、ここんな感じ！
The mosaic is already like this!
逆にやばい！
It's dangerously the opposite!
やばい、やばい、やばい、やばい、やばい！
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous!
可愛い。
Cute.
どんどん行こう、どんどん行こう。えーと、
Let's keep going, keep going. Um—
じゃ、ラストは、やっぱアイドルだからさ、チョコ線アイドル、とびきりの可愛いアイドル、お願いします！
Well, for the last one, since we're idols, Choco-sen idol, a super cute idol, please!
あい！
Ai!
え、可愛い！
Eh, cute!
いや、これは、あ、いいねです。
No, this is... Ah, that's nice.
かわいいー
So cute!
アップ、顔のアップいいね。
An up-close face shot is nice.
たまらんです。
It's irresistible.
おっけー、いっぱいいただけたー
Okay, I got lots of them!
ありがと、ありがとー
Thank you, thank you!
いや、ちょっとね、この続きはちょっとメン限でやらせていただきますので。
Well, the rest will be for members-only, so...
メン限ではちょっと歌も、撮影会も、シチュエーションドラマもなんと2本やっちゃいまーす！
In the members-only stream, we'll do singing, a photoshoot, and two situation dramas!
楽しみだ！
I'm looking forward to it!
ちなみにさ、なんかタイトルとかあんの、そのシチュエーションドラマって？
By the way, does the situation drama have a title?
あ、今回のタイトルが、先生とベッドで特別バレンタインー
Ah, this time the title is: Special Valentine with the Teacher in Bed...
特別バレンタインってタイトルと、あと
Special Valentine, and...
診察室で甘い処方箋をって言う...
...sweet prescriptions in the examination room.
メセンもちょっとカメラマンさんをベッドに横たわらせて、ちょっとみんなが本当に、あの、本当に見えるように、
Also, having the cameraman lie down on the bed so everyone can really see up close...
さっかくが追いかぶさられるように、色んな角度で撮っていきたいと思います！
...being hovered over, taking pictures from various angles!
楽しみ！お楽しみにー！
Exciting! Look forward to it!
ということで、そろそろお時間が迫ってきたので、ちょっとライブの方に戻りたいと思います。
So, since it's almost time, we'd like to get back to the live.
この気持ちでね、ちょっとライブだった。そうだ、急げー！
With this feeling, right, it's the live. That's right, hurry!
いそげー！いそげー！
Hurry! Hurry!
ということで、このあと二人それぞれちょっとデュエットしてもらうんだけど、最後に3人でも歌うので楽しみにしててください。
And with that, after this the two of them will do a duet, and finally the three of us will sing together, so please look forward to it.
それでは違いに行きましょうか。おっ、あ、これ！すごい！こうてん、えりもついてる。可愛い！
Well then, shall we go to the other side? Oh, wow, this! Amazing! It has a sailor collar too. Cute!
じゃあちょっとカーテンの裏で二人でお着替えしてきまーす。
Well then, the two of us will go change behind the curtain.
それでは聞いてください。
Now then, please listen.
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
ドロドロとろり Baby
Melty, melting, Baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だりん
Melt and Catch me, darling
ピュアピュアココアふわふわきゅるきゅる 1,2
Pure pure cocoa, fluffy, sparkling 1,2
なんか眠れない夜にはお散歩
Taking a walk on a sleepless night
特別パーティタイム 二人きり
Special party time, just the two of us
あの角曲げれば
If we turn that corner,
ベンチしかない公園だよ
it's a park with only a bench.
蒸し暑い空気の中 迷い込むんだ
Wandering into the humid air
コンビニちょっと寄り道
Dropping by the convenience store
アイスじゃなくて、これがいい
instead of ice cream, this is good.
缶のお酒ほろ酔い ウィンクでストロング！
Tipsy on canned alcohol, strong with a wink!
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラブで壊して
Can't get drunk on liqueur anymore, break it with love
お砂糖はマシマシで 飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra sugar, don't need ease of drinking
灼熱でさ、溶け出して？ ごくって飲んで
Melting in the scorching heat? Drink it right down
癖のある私のことを 大事にしてよね
Take good care of quirky little me
サマーチョコレート ドロドロとろり Baby
Summer Chocolate, melty, melting Baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だりん
Melt and Catch me, darling
ピュアピュアココアふわふわきゅるきゅる
Pure pure cocoa, fluffy, sparkling
ちょっと寂しい帰り道ふらふら
Wandering swayingly on the slightly lonely way back
特別ボーナスタイム 手を繋ごう
Special bonus time, let's hold hands
大きめTシャツ 君に借りた
An oversized T-shirt I borrowed from you
ありがとうって 匂わせみたいにして
Saying thank you like a subtle hint
困らせたいんだ
I want to tease you.
コンビニまた寄っちゃって もう一本だけの弱いやつ
Stopping by the convenience store again for one more weak drink
つるつるりんメルティ テンパリングが重要！
Smooth melty, tempering is important!
熱すぎでも飽きちゃって 冷たいのはダメ
Getting bored if too hot, cold is no good
チョコみたいな私を プレシャスにして
Make chocolate-like me precious
ビターさんの酒で シュワシュワシュワシュワ～
With bitter alcohol, shh-shh-shh-shh~
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach unless conveyed
恋してる証拠に ここでチュウってして
As proof of love, kiss me right here
夜空のグラスにキラキラこぼして
Spilling sparkles into the night sky glass
息もできないくらいにもう だって...
To the point of breathless, because...
恋に溺れて 君の熱でとけたら
Drowning in love, if I melt in your heat
そのまんまで食べてよ 手にベタベタついちゃって
Eat me just as I am, getting sticky on your hands
一生一緒
Together forever
缶のお酒ほろ酔い ウィンクでストロング！
Tipsy on canned alcohol, strong with a wink!
リキュールじゃもう酔えない ラブで壊して
Can't get drunk on liqueur anymore, break it with love
お砂糖はマシマシで 飲みやすさとかいらない
Extra sugar, don't need ease of drinking
灼熱でさ、溶け出して？ ごくって飲んで
Melting in the scorching heat? Drink it right down
癖のある私だからさ 君が選ばれた
Because quirky me is why you were chosen
サマーチョコレート ドロドロとろり Baby
Summer Chocolate, melty, melting Baby
とろけちゃって Catch me だりん
Melt and Catch me, darling
ピュアピュアココアふわふわきゅるきゅる 1,2
Pure pure cocoa, fluffy, sparkling 1,2
サマーチョコレート
Summer Chocolate
どろどろどろりべっぴし
Melty, melty, baby
とろけちゃってcatch meだーりん
Melting, catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあここあふふわりきゅるきゅる
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffy, spinning 'round
なんか眠れない夜にはお散歩
For some reason, on a night I can't sleep, a walk
特別パーティータイム2人きり(やったー)
Special party time, just the two of us (Yay!)
あの角曲がれば
If you turn that corner,
ベンチしかない公園だよ
it's just a park with a bench
蒸し暑い空気の中迷い込むんだ
Getting lost in the humid air
コンビニちょっと寄り道(買い出し)
A little detour to the convenience store
アイスじゃなくてこれがいい
Not ice cream, I want this
缶のお酒ほろ酔いウインクですとろんぐ!
Canned alcohol, a little tipsy, a wink, it's strong!
リキュールじゃもう酔えないラブで壊して(お願いい)
Liqueur won't make me drunk anymore, crush me with love (please)
お砂糖はマシマシで飲みやすさとかいらない
Sugar is doubled, I don't need it to be easy to drink
炙熱でさ、溶かして?
In the scorching heat, melt it?
ごくって飲んで
Drink it in one gulp
クセのある私のことを大事にしてよねサマーチョコレート
Please cherish me, as I have my quirks, Summer Chocolate
どろどろどろりべっぴし
Melty, melty, baby
とろけちゃってcatch meだーりん
Melting, catch me, darling
ぴゅあぴゅあここあふふわりきゅるきゅる
Pure, pure, cocoa, fluffy, spinning 'round
ちょっと寂しい帰り道ふらふら
A little lonely on the way home, staggering
特別ボーナスタイム手を繋ごう(にゃんにゃん)
Special bonus time, let's hold hands (meow meow)
大きめTシャツ君に借りたありがとーって匂わせみたいにして
Wearing a large t-shirt I borrowed from you, saying "thank you"
困らせたいんだ
I want to make you troubled by acting like I'm hinting at something
コンビニまた寄りくちゃって(楽しい)
Stopped by the convenience store again (it's fun)
もう1本だけのよわいやつ
Just one more, a weaker one
とぅるとぅるりんにメルティテンパリングが大事!
Turu turu ring, melty, tempering is important!
アツすぎても飽きちゃって冷たいのはダメ(やだももん)
Even if it's too hot, I get bored of it, I don't like cold things
チョコみたいな私をプレシャスにして扱って
Please treat me preciously, just like chocolate
微炭酸のお酒でしゅわしゅわしゅわしゅわ～
With lightly carbonated alcohol, fizz, fizz, fizz~
愛は伝えなきゃ届かない
Love won't reach if you don't convey it
恋してる証拠にここでちゅーってして
Kiss me right here as proof that I love you
夜空のグラスにキラキラ満溢して息もできないくらいにもう
Spilling glitter into the glass of the night sky, until I can't even breathe anymore
だって…恋に溺れて君の熱で溶けたらそのまんまで食べてよ
Drowning in love, if I melt from your heat, eat me just like that
手にベトベト貼り付いちゃって一生いっしょ
Sticky all over my hands, together forever
缶のお酒ほろ酔いウインクですとろんぐ!
Canned alcohol, a little tipsy, a wink, it's strong!
リキュールじゃもう酔えないラブで壊して(お願いい)
Liqueur won't make me drunk anymore, crush me with love (please)
お砂糖はマシマシで飲みやすさとかいらない
Sugar is doubled, I don't need it to be easy to drink
炙熱でさ、溶かして?ごくって飲んで
In the scorching heat, melt it? Drink it in one gulp
クセのある私だからさ君が選ばれたサマーチョコレート
Because I have my quirks, you were chosen, Summer Chocolate
あなたのことが好きなのに私にまるで見所いない
I like you, but you're not interested in me at all
何回目かの失恋の準備 Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
I'm already preparing for my bajillionth heartbreak, Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
I look around and see tons of cute girls
地味な花は気づいてくれない Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
You don't notice a plain flower like me, Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテラ流れるMusicぼんやり聴いていたら
Before I know it, I start tapping to the beat
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせてつま先から動き出す
While listening absentmindedly to the music playing in the cafeteria
止められない今の気持ち
Can't stop how I feel right now
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー 占ってよ
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon baby, tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー!未来はそんな悪くないよ Hey! Hey! Hey!
Fortune cookie in love! The future's not so bad, Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
Gotta let him see you smile to bring luck your way
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of my heart
運勢今日よりもよくしよう Hey! Hey! Hey!
Gonna make my luck even better than it was today, Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! 人生捨てたもんじゃないよね あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
Hey! Hey! Hey! Life's not a lost cause, shocking miracles do happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I've got a hunch we'll fall in love
あなたにちゃんと告りたいだけど自分に自信がない
I wanna confess how I feel to you, but I'm not very confident in myself
リアクションは想像つくから Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Because I can already imagine how you'll react, Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いいコがいいなんて男の子は言うけどルックスがアドバンテージ
Guys say they like girls with good personalities, but looks are an advantage
いつだって可愛いコが人気投票1位になる
Cute girls are the ones who always rank 1st in popularity contests
プリーズ プリーズ プリーズ オーベイビー 私も見て
Please, please, please, oh baby, look at me too
恋するフォーチュンクッキー!その殻 さあ壊してみよう Hey! Hey! Hey!
Fortune cookie in love! C'mon, break through your shell, Hey! Hey! Hey!
先の展開 神様も知らない
Not even god knows how things will unfold
涙のフォーチュンクッキー!そんなにネガティブにならずに Hey! Hey! Hey!
Fortune cookie in tears! Don't be so negative, Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! 世界は愛で溢れているよ
Hey! Hey! Hey! The world's full of love
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
I'll make you forget everything sad that's happened
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
Different winds will blow tomorrow
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー 占ってよ
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon baby, tell my fortune
恋するフォーチュンクッキー!未来はそんな悪くないよ Hey! Hey! Hey!
Fortune cookie in love! The future's not so bad, Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
Gotta let him see you smile to bring luck your way
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of my heart
運勢今日よりもよくしよう Hey! Hey! Hey!
Gonna make my luck even better than it was today, Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! 人生捨てたもんじゃないよね あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
Hey! Hey! Hey! Life's not a lost cause, shocking miracles do happen
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I've got a hunch we'll fall in love
あなたのこと好きなのに
I like you,
私にまるで興味ない
yet you have no interest in me at all.
何度目かの失恋の準備
Preparing for my umpteenth heartbreak,
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
まわりを見れば大勢の
I look around and see tons of
可愛いコたちがいるんだもん
cute girls all around.
地味な花は気づいてくれない
You don't notice a plain flower like me.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
カフェテリア流れるMusic
Music playing in the cafeteria
ぼんやり聴いていたら
While listening absentmindedly
知らぬ間にリズムに合わせ
Before I know it, tapping to the beat
つま先から動き出す
Moving from the tips of my toes
止められない今の気持ち
Can't stop how I feel right now.
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー
C'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon baby
占ってよ
Tell my fortune,
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
Fortune cookie in love!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future's not so bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
Gotta let him see you smile to bring luck your way.
ハートのフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie of my heart,
運勢 今日よりよくしよう
Gonna make my luck even better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
人生捨てたもんじゃないよね
Life's not a lost cause,
あっと驚く奇跡が起きる
Shocking miracles do happen.
あなたとどこかで愛し合える予感
I've got a hunch we'll fall in love somewhere.
あなたにちゃんと伝えたい
I want to properly tell you how I feel,
だけど自分に自信がない
but I have no confidence in myself.
リアクションは想像つくから
Because I can already imagine your reaction.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
性格いいコがいいなんて
Guys say they like girls with good personalities,
男の人は言うけれど
but looks are an advantage.
ルックスがアドバンテージ
Cute girls are always
いつだって可愛いコが
ranked 1st in popularity.
人気投票1位になる
プリーズ プリーズ プリーズ オーベイビー
Please please please oh baby,
私も見て
look at me too.
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
Fortune cookie in love!
その殻さあ壊してみよう
Break through your shell.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
先の展開神様も知らない
Not even God knows how things will unfold.
涙のフォーチュンクッキー
Fortune cookie in tears!
そんなにネガティブにならずに
Don't be so negative.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
世界は愛で溢れているよ
The world's full of love.
悲しい出来事忘れさせる
I'll make you forget everything sad.
明日は明日の風が吹くと思う
Tomorrow is another day.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
カモン カモン カモン カモン ベイビー
C'mon c'mon c'mon c'mon baby,
占ってよ
tell my fortune,
恋するフォーチュンクッキー！
Fortune cookie in love!
未来はそんな悪くないよ
The future's not so bad.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
ツキを呼ぶには笑顔を見せること
Gotta let him see you smile to bring luck your way.
運勢 今日よりよくしよう
Gonna make my luck even better than today.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
君が好きったら君が好き
If you like someone, you like them!
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love...
あのね乙女は本気出すと凄いんです
You know, when maidens get serious, they're amazing!
いつかいつづけてあの手この手で
Using every trick in the book one day,
ライバルを出し抜くの
outwitting the rivals.
全部計算済みレシピ通り
Everything is calculated just like the recipe!
好きだ 手抜きにしないで
Don't half-ass your love!
意地悪言って見たりして
Trying to be a bit mean,
ぐっと無理して甘えて
or acting boldly and sweetly.
すでにピンチ？
Already in a desperate spot?
つまみ食いしたらなくなった
Snuck a bite and it's all gone!
恨んでやる 日本酒 ときに反旗
I'll resent you, sake, raising a rebellion at times.
苦いのはNGで
Bitter things are a no-go,
女の子の季節だもん全部思い通りになってよね
It's a girl's season, so everything should go just as I want!
君は私と結ばれます
You will be bound to me!
本命あげちゃうメルティー
Giving you my true-feelings Valentine's chocolate, Melty!
誰にも渡さない大戦争
A great war where I won't hand you over to anyone!
おトキめいちゃいますメルシー
My heart flutters, merci!
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃう？大丈夫ですと？
So, shall we hold hands? Is that okay?
スキスキスキ 甘くっていいの？
Like, like, like! Is it okay if it's sweet?
スキスキスキ はっ
Like, like, like! Ha!
こういうのが一生の片想いなんざもん絶対譲らない覚悟です
This kind of lifelong unrequited love—I'm resolved never to give it up!
本気なのです
I'm serious!
目を見て言って君の気持ち
Look me in the eyes and tell me your feelings!
ピュアラブ ピュアラブ
Pure love, pure love...
ガールズバトルフィーバー
Girls' battle fever!
（あのさこないだ喋ってんの？）
Hey, were you talking the other day?
ガールズバトルフィーバー
Girls' battle fever!
（推しの子がショックダウン！）
My oshi got shocked down!
ガールズバトルフィーバー
Girls' battle fever!
（大丈夫？百足れないもん！）
Are you okay? It's not enough!
骨抜きにされたが勝ちなのです
Whoever gets charmed wins!
甘いのがゼロなら食べちゃいな！
If there's zero sweetness, just eat it up!
砂糖の量は愛の量！
The amount of sugar is the amount of love!
間違えたこれ塩だった！
Oops, I mistook this for salt!
まごころ心
A sincere heart,
調理室で手伝ってはいる
helping out in the kitchen.
まごころ込めてラッピング
Wrapping it with sincere feelings,
自分も本気モードでいく
Going into serious mode myself!
祈るラッピーちゃん
Praying, Rappy-chan!
何度も試作した
I've made trial after trial
横暴練習もした
and practiced repeatedly,
弱気になってなるな 大丈夫自分上等
Don't get faint-hearted, I'm at my best!
女子道 一番 可愛い私なんだから
It's the girl's way, 'cause I'm the cutest me!
君は私と結ばれます
You will be bound to me,
結ばれる運命なのです
it is our fated destiny!
本命上げちゃう めるてぃー！ 誰にも渡さない大戦争
Giving you my true love, meltie! A great war where I won't let anyone have you!
ときめいちゃいます？めしー♡
Does your heart flutter? Merci ♡
それじゃ手とか繋いじゃう？内緒のデート
Shall we hold hands then? A secret date.
すうぃーでぃーすうぃーでぃーきす
Sweetie sweetie kiss
(ちゅ！ちゅ！)
(Chu! Chu!)
甘くていいの？
Is being sweet okay?
すうぃーでぃーすうぃーでぃーはぐ (ぎゅ！ぎゅ！)
Sweetie sweetie hug (Gyu! Gyu!)
こういうのがいいっしょ？
Isn't this kind of thing nice?
初恋なんだもん絶対譲れない覚悟なのです本気なのです
It's my first love, so I'm resolved never to yield, I'm serious!
目を見て言って？君の気持ち
Look in my eyes and say it? Your feelings
ぴゅあらぴゅあら ぴゅあらぴゅあら ぴゅあらぴゅあら ぴゅあらぶ
Pure pure pure pure love...
はーい、ということで、チョコたち3人の新曲でしたー！
Hii, so that was the new song by us three, Choco-tachi!
イエーイ！イエーイ！新曲でしたー！
Yay! Yay! It was a new song!
改めまして、ノエルさんは、ラミィさんと一緒にね、コラボ歌唱をした
Once again, Noel-san, together with Lamy-san, you collaborated on vocals for
『初恋大戦争』という新曲なんですけど、
this new song called "Hatsukoi Daisensou",
今回作詞作曲をメダン様、そして編曲を洋介様に、おねがいいたしましたー！
and this time, the lyrics and composition were by Medan-sama, and arrangement by Yousuke-sama!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございますー！
Thank you so much!
いや、今回のテーマが、バレンタインの日に、3人の可愛い女の子たちが、1人の男の子を手に入れるために、バチバチにね、出し抜き合おうとするみたいな、
The theme this time is about how on Valentine's Day, three cute girls fiercely try to outmaneuver each other to get a single boy,
聞き応えのある手厚い楽曲となっております！
resulting in a very substantial and engaging song!
いいね、可愛い。可愛い。そう。
That's right, cute. Cute. Exactly.
いやもう3人の声が合わさって、めちゃめちゃアイドルソングになっているので、
Yeah, and with the three voices blending, it has become such an idol song,
ぜひぜひ皆さま聞いてください！
so everyone please be sure to listen to it!
聞いてねー！
Listen to it!
え、何回も聞きたいな。ね、何回も聞いてたくさん聴けるところもあるかな。
Uh, I want to listen to it over and over. Right, there are places where you can listen to it many times.
いやこちらの楽曲は、この後24時から2月15日0時からね、各種音楽サイトにて配信されます！やったー！聞ける！
And this song will be distributed on various music sites starting tonight at midnight, February 15th at 0:00! Yay! You can listen to it!
手を叩きます。そしてね、この配信後すぐに、この楽曲のMVが公開されます！やったー！
Clapping our hands. And right after this broadcast, the MV for this song will be released! Yay!
いやぜひぜひ皆さまいっぱい聞いて、MVの方にもちょっと感想とかね、コメントいただけたら嬉しいなって思います！
Yes, please listen to it a lot, and we'd be so happy if you could leave some impressions and comments on the MV as well!
見てねー！お願いします！お願いします！
Please check it out! Please! Please!
じゃあね、2人とも今日はありがとう！
Well then, thank you both for today!
お誕生日おめでとう！ありがとー！嬉しい！
Happy birthday! Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
引き続きね、応援してくだね！頑張る！ありがとー！
Please continue to support us! I'll do my best! Thank you!
おさらばじゃ！おさらば！おさらば！ありがとー！
Farewell! Farewell! Farewell! Thank you!
そしてここからライブ後半となります！まだまだゲストパートとか、なんと最後に重大告知もあるので、皆様一緒に楽しんでいきましょう！それでは、次のゲストは…こちら！
And from here on is the second half of the live! There are still guest parts, and even a major announcement at the very end, so let's all enjoy it together! Well then, our next guest is... right here!
大人のフリして。
Playing the adult.
急に会いたいって いつものように準備してる 午前0時すぎの終電で向かう帰り道
Saying you want to see me suddenly, I get ready as usual. Heading home on the last train just past midnight.
やめておきなって言われても
Even if I'm told to stop it,
まっさらな街にゆく会いたいから
Meeting up again, let's go somewhere new.
別々に落ち合う
Separately falling in love,
街の風は少し冷たい
the city breeze is a bit chilly.
慣れないうちは無理やり飲み干してしまってはふらふわ
If we aren't used to it, forcing it won't work,
ふらわ
floating away.
ちればれちゃったらどうしよう
If we fall apart, what should we do?
へたにしちゃったらどうしよう
If we get too awkward, what should we do?
少しも覗きたくない
I don't even want to see you slightly upset.
ちょっと期待してね？
Just a bit conceited, eh?
ずっと見え透いてね？
Always staying out of reach, eh?
周りばかり気にして生きてる
You only care about what's around you.
ちょっと優越感、でもね
Always acting superior, eh?
なんだかみすぼらしくて、あぁ
It's kind of miserable, ah.
本当は自分じゃいい気がして
I really wish I was just being myself.
いつも分かったふりして
Always pretending to understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself when I shouldn't.
街のしない傷でも
Even with clumsy scars,
やっぱ一番嬉しくて
right now I'm the happiest.
とびきりの私はかわいいかな
"Are you cute?" I wonder.
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight is bound to break us apart.
なんにも消えそうな糸で繋がってる恋だね
Connected by invisible threads,
私は諦めたらきっと簡単に消えちゃうね
if I give up, I bet it'll easily vanish.
引き止めるにはどうする？
To stop it, what should I do?
足手まといだったらどうする？
If I'm useless, what should I do?
不器用に嫉妬を絡めてさ
Clumsily letting my jealousy show.
いつもチェックしてね？
Always checking in, eh?
いつも息自由でね？
Always breathing freely, eh?
他のこと比べてばかりいた
Comparing myself to everyone else.
一番見て欲しい、あぁ
I want you to only look at me, ah.
どこか違う景色見てる
Looking at the scenery somewhere else.
いつものは優しいふりして
Always putting on a gentle act,
そんなんじゃないのに笑って
laughing when I shouldn't be.
近づけば近づくほど
Getting a little closer,
心は遠く感じて
feeling our hearts ache a bit more.
少しずつ離れて、こと分かるよ
Even with those clumsy steps, I get it.
今夜は忘れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight is bound to break us apart.
自分をもっと強ければ
If we want to get closer,
それはさよならを言えるのにさ
being clumsy is the only way to say it.
いつも分かったふりして
Always acting like I understand,
そんなんじゃないのに無理して
forcing myself when I shouldn't.
ふと見せる優しさが
Your kind smile is something
ずっと忘れられなくて
I'll never be able to forget.
とりつくろった私はかわいいかな
Being by your side, I wonder if I'm cute?
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight is bound to break us apart.
突然放たれた日
Suddenly left behind,
私がまた揺れて
I'm stumbling all over again.
いつか振り向いてくれてるとおもっていたもういいから
Looking back, you were always there.
とりつくろった私の中なんてゆく
With clumsy steps, I'll keep going.
今夜は壊れるほど抱きしめて
Tonight is bound to break us apart.
chocolate box
なんかいつも眠そうだし
You always look like you're sleepy.
なんかいつもつまんなさそうだし
You always look bored.
なんかいつもヤバそうだし
You always look reckless.
なんかいつもスマホいじってるし
You're always messing with your phone.
ホントはテンション高いのに
You act like you're full of energy,
アタシといると超低いし
but with me, you're super low.
なんなん自分？ありえなくない？
What kind of self is that? Unacceptable!
嫌い、大嫌い。どうでもいい！！
I hate you, I despise you, whatever!
だったらボクも言うけどさ！！
If that's how it is, I'll say it too!
ちっちゃいことで すぐ怒りし
You get mad over tiny things,
言い返したら すぐ泣くし
and cry the moment you talk back.
ごめんって言っても許してくれないし
Even when you say sorry, you never forgive me.
その割一晩が明けちゃえば
Yet once the night clears up,
ケロッとおはようとか言うし
you act like everything's totally fine.
あぁ なんて罪深い人なんだ
Ah, what a sinful person you are.
畜生！！もう知らないぞ！！
Damn it, I'm done with you!
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
Sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレート
secret chocolate with a cosmic taste.
二人だけのデコレーションを散りばめて
Scattering our unique decoration,
彩っで食べちゃおうか！！
let's color it and eat it up!
コレクション 切り分けて彩って食べちゃおうか
Let's slice up the collection and eat it up!
苦い苦い愛の甘たまて箱
A bitter-sweet Pandora's box of love
未来味の不思議なチョコレートと
With a mysterious chocolate of future flavor
温めて混ぜたらきっと
If you warm and mix it up, I'm sure
いつかお口に合う味になるの
It will eventually suit your taste.
ねえねえ ちょっといいかな
"Hey, hey, do you have a minute?"
なんだ？ さっきはあのね ごめんね
"What? About just now... um, sorry."
なにが？ いつももやっとなるじゃん
"What's that? You're always so vague."
それで？
"So?"
今日はこれを渡したくて 言葉じゃ足りないからさ
"Today I wanted to give you this, and words aren't enough."
だから？
"So?"
受け取ってくれないかな
"Won't you accept it?"
なにを？
"What is it?"
一緒にしれくれてありがとう
"Thanks for being with me!"
あなたの優しさに ついつい甘えちゃお
I tend to indulge in your kindness.
誰よりも近いから 素直になれない
You're closer than anyone, so I can't be honest.
昨日は一生懸命そう ついつい忘れちゃう
Yesterday I tried my best, but I always forget.
誰よりも一番大好きなのに
Even though I love you more than anyone else!
甘い甘い夢の宝箱
A sweet, sweet dream treasure box,
奇跡味のナイショのチョコレートと
With a secret chocolate of miracle flavor,
ふたりだけのイノベーションを探し組み立てたら賑わおうか
If we search for and assemble our own innovation, let's make it lively!
苦い苦い日々の化粧箱
A bitter-sweet vanity case of daily life,
世界味の最初のチョコレートと
With the very first chocolate of world flavor,
喚き聞いて割れないように大事に包んで障がいの完成まで
Wrapping it carefully so it doesn't break until the completion of our obstacle.
いつだって やめるときも
Whenever we stop,
どんな時も 想像と
At any time, with imagination,
健やかなときも 病めるときも違うふたりを分かつまで
In sickness and in health, until we are separated, two different people.
愛してる 僕もそうさ
"I love you." "I do too."
そばにいて そばにいる
"Stay by my side." "I'm by your side."
なんて嘘かむよ あ、そうかい僕も適当に行った
"What a lie!" "Oh really? I just said it casually."
甘い甘い 苦い苦い
Sweet, sweet, bitter, bitter!
甘い甘い恋の魔法箱
A sweet, sweet magic box of love,
宇宙味の秘密のチョコレートと
With a secret chocolate of space flavor,
ふたりだけのデコレーションを切り分けて彩って食べちゃおうか
If we slice up and color our own decoration, let's eat it up!
苦い苦い愛の甘たまて箱
A bitter-sweet Pandora's box of love,
未来味の不思議なチョコレートと
With a mysterious chocolate of future flavor,
温めて混ぜたら絶対 いつか最高に幸せな味になるの
If we warm and mix it up, it will definitely become the happiest taste someday!
せーの でっかいキューソマンシータイム
On the count of three, a huge "so much time"!
ねえ 一つだけ聞いていい 私のこと
Hey, can I ask you just one thing? About me...
告白日和、です！
It's a confession day!
会えるかも今日は 心が騒いで スキップしたくなった
Maybe we can meet today? My heart fluttered, and I wanted to skip.
ときめきに躍る瞬間 私のことなど 多分気にしてないのだろうけど
In this moment dancing with excitement, you probably don't even care about me, but...
ここにいるんだよ 私はだから
I'm right here, you know.
自信が揺れ動く 嫌われてないかな? 勢いでとにかく挨拶だ!
My self-confidence wavers. Do you dislike me? I'll just greet you with all my energy!
やっと晴れたね ぱーっと晴れたね そして元気になるね
It's finally sunny, it's brightly sunny, and I feel energized!
おはようの代わりに背中を叩いて 「さあ、行くよ!」
Instead of saying "good morning," I pat your back and say, "Now, let's go!"
やっと晴れたら ぱーっと晴れたら きっと元気な笑顔
When it's finally sunny, when it's brightly sunny, I'm sure you'll have a cheerful smile.
なんだか今のこの気持ちが切なくなったよ 授業の上空 遠目を眺めた
For some reason, this feeling right now became so bittersweet. During class, I gazed far off into the sky.
恋って甘いもんじゃない? 違うかも つらさ半分 夢見るだけより 触って確かめなきゃ
Isn't love supposed to be sweet? Maybe not, it's half painful. Rather than just dreaming, I have to touch and find out.
だから…動き出そうよ 自分らしくね 楽しく生きるの 毎日がキセキ
So... let's make a move, being true to ourselves. Living happily, every day is a miracle.
言わずに悔やむより勇気を出そう! ずっと前から うんと前から 聞いてみたいて待ってた
Rather than regretting in silence, let's muster up courage! Always, from long ago, very much from long ago, I've been waiting, wanting to ask you.
私から最初に伝えてしまえ 「大好きです!」
I'll be the first to tell you: "I love you!"
ずっと前だよ うんと前だよ 聞いたことに答えて? どんなふうに感じているの 全部見せてよ!
It's been a long time, very much a long time. Answer what I asked! Show me everything about how you feel!
君が好きっなら君が好き！
If I love you, if I love you!
ひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあぶ
Pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara
あのね 乙女は 本気を出すと すごいんです
Hey, a maiden is serious when she puts in effort, it's amazing.
うおうんちゅ いずれ 手中
I want you, sooner or later, in my grasp.
あの手この手で ライバルを出し抜くの
I'll outsmart my rival with this trick or that.
全部計算済み！ レシピ通り
Everything is calculated! Just like the recipe.
「セクシーだって 武器にして」
"Let's use sexiness as a weapon."
「呟いてみたりして」
"Let's try whispering."
「酔ったふりで 甘えて」
"Let's pretend to be drunk and act sweet."
既に デッドヒート
It's already a dead heat.
「ぁ、ぁ、ぁ、ぁ、ぁ、ぁ、ぁ、 寝坊した」
"Ah, ah, ah, I overslept."
「つまみ食いしたら なくなった！？」
"I snuck a bite and now it's gone!?"
「ブランデー？ いや 日本酒！」
"Brandy? No, sake!"
ときに ファンキー
Sometimes funky.
苦いのは NGで
Bitter things are a no-go.
女の子の季節だもん
It's a girl's season, after all.
全部思い通りになってよね
Everything will go as I wish.
君は 私と 結ばれます
You will be mine.
本命あげちゃう めるとぃー！
I'll give you my true feelings, Melty!
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
A great war that I won't lose to anyone.
ときめいちゃいます？ めりしー♡
Will it make your heart flutter? Merci 🤍
それじゃ 手とか 繋いじまう？ 内緒のデート
Shall we hold hands then? A secret date.
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー きす (ちゅ！ ちゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, kiss (Chu! Chu!)
甘くていいの
It's okay to be sweet.
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー はぐ (ぎゅ！ ぎゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, hug (Gyu! Gyu!)
こういうのが いいっしょ？
This kind of thing is good, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対 譲らない 覚悟です
It's my first love, I'm determined not to give up.
本気なのです
I'm serious.
目を見て 言って？ 君の気持ち
Look me in the eye and say it? Your feelings.
ひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあぶ
Pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー きす (ちゅ！ ちゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, kiss (Chu! Chu!)
甘くていいの
It's okay to be sweet.
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー はぐ (ぎゅ！ ぎゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, hug (Gyu! Gyu!)
こういうのが いいっしょ？
This kind of thing is good, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対 譲らない 覚悟です
It's my first love, I'm determined not to give up.
本気なのです
I'm serious.
目を見て 言って？ 君の気持ち
Look me in the eye and say it? Your feelings.
ひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあぶ
Pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battlefield
「何で 彼と 喋ってんの！？」
"Why are you talking to him!?"
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battlefield
「一瞬 思考が ショート no!!」
"My thoughts just shorted out, no!!"
ガールズバトルフィールド
Girls' battlefield
「大丈夫 へこたれないもの」
"It's okay, I won't give up."
惚れさせたが 勝ちです
The one who makes him fall for them wins.
「鼻血が出るほど 食べちゃない？」
"Eat until your nose bleeds?"
「砂糖の量は 愛の量」
"The amount of sugar is the amount of love."
「間違えた！ これ 塩だった」
"I messed up! This was salt."
ま ご乱心
Well, a bit crazy.
正直 ドキドキしてはいる
Honestly, I am nervous.
真心 こめて ラッピング
自分も 本気 コーデで 行く
I'll go in my best outfit.
祈る ラブリーチチャンス
Praying for a lovely chance.
何度も 試作した 予行練習もした
I practiced and rehearsed many times.
弱気になりなさんな
Don't be timid.
大丈夫 自分史上1番かわいい私 なんだから！
It's okay, I'm the cutest version of myself in history!
君は 私と 結ばれます
You will be mine.
結ばれる 運命なのです
It's my fate to be yours.
本命あげちゃう めるとぃー！
I'll give you my true feelings, Melty!
誰にも渡さない 大戦争
A great war that I won't lose to anyone.
ときめいちゃいます？ めりしー♡
Will it make your heart flutter? Merci 🤍
それじゃ 手とか 繋いじまう？ 内緒のデート
Shall we hold hands then? A secret date.
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー きす (ちゅ！ ちゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, kiss (Chu! Chu!)
甘くていいの
It's okay to be sweet.
すぅーてぃーぅーすぅーてぃーぅー はぐ (ぎゅ！ ぎゅ！)
Sweetie, sweetie, hug (Gyu! Gyu!)
こういうのが いいっしょ？
This kind of thing is good, right?
初恋なんだもん 絶対 譲らない 覚悟です
It's my first love, I'm determined not to give up.
本気なのです
I'm serious.
目を見て 言って？ 君の気持ち
Look me in the eye and say it? Your feelings.
ひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあらひゅあぶ
Pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara pyuara
世界は恋に落ちている
My world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射る
An arrow of light pierces my chest
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you
「ねえ、教えて」
"Hey, tell me"
すれ違う言葉にちょっとだけの後悔
I have a few regrets about the words we passed each other by with
涙こぼれて
Tears spill over
忙しい感情 鼓動にリンクする
Link my busy emotions to my heartbeat
チューニング確かめたいんだ
I want to confirm the tuning
目的ばかにとらわれて
Caught up in just the goal
大事なものが霞んで逃げて
The important things haze over and run away
今日もリスタート
Today, I'll restart again
世界は恋に落ちている
My world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射る
An arrow of light pierces my chest
全部わかりたいんだよ
I want to understand everything
「ねえ、聞かせて」
"Hey, let me hear it"
たった1ミリが遠くて
Just 1 millimeter is too far
駆け抜けれた日々に
And in the days I ran through
忘れない忘れられない 輝く1ページ
I can't forget, I can't forget the shining first page
お似合いの二人になんだか複雑な
I'm a bit conflicted about the two of you being a good match
気持ちがいるよ
I have a feeling
初めての感情 鼓動にリンクする
My first time having these emotions, linking to my heartbeat
体温計 壊れちゃったかな?
I wonder if my thermometer is broken?
自分のこと分からないまま
Without understanding myself
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I even gave advice to that girl
胸が痛いよ...
My chest hurts...
世界は恋に落ちている
My world is falling in love
光の矢胸を射る
An arrow of light pierces my chest
気付けたこの想いは
This feeling I've realized
「もう、遅いの」
"It's already too late"
あの子の方が可愛いのは知ってるよだけど
I know that girl is cuter, but
君のこと全部分かりたいって思ってしまう
I find myself thinking that I want to understand everything about you
これが恋って初めて気づいたの
I realized for the first time that this is love
絶対振り向いてほしい
I definitely want you to turn to me
遅かったけど諦めたくない
It was late, but I don't want to give up
だって、好きだから
Because I love you
ホントの気持ち言葉にして
If I could put my true feelings into words
大事なこと話せたら
And tell you the important things
今日もリスタート
Today, I'll restart again
鈍感な君だから
Because you are thick-headed
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
The world is falling in love, an arrow of light piercing my chest.
君をわかりたいんだよ
I want to understand you.
自分のことわからないまま
Without even understanding myself,
あの子にアドバイスまでしちゃって
I ended up giving that girl advice...
胸が痛いわ
My heart aches.
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
The world is falling in love, an arrow of light piercing my chest,
気づいたこの想いは
and these feelings I've realized...
あの子の方が可愛いのは知ってるけれど
I know that girl is cuter, but
意気地なしよだけど
I'm so cowardly, yet
うまくいかないでなんてね
saying "I hope things don't go well for you,"
逃げ出したいくせに
even though I want to run away.
バカ
Idiot.
君のこと全部わかりたいって思っちゃう
I find myself wanting to know everything about you,
これが恋だって初めて気づいたの
and I realized for the first time that this is love.
絶対振り向いてほしい 遅かったけどあきらめたくない
I definitely want you to turn around. Even though it's late, I don't want to give up.
だって、好きなんだもん
Because I love you.
春に咲いた花が恋をした 花は必死に上を向いて笑った
A flower that bloomed in spring fell in love, looking upward and smiling desperately.
青い夏の蕾も恋をした 咲かない花と火薬の匂い
A bud in the blue summer also fell in love, an unblooming flower and the scent of gunpowder.
本当の気持ち言葉にして 大事なこと話せたら
If I can turn my true feelings into words and talk about what matters,
鈍感な君だから口に出して言わなくちゃ
You're a bit dense, so I have to say it out loud.
本当の気持ち言葉にして 大事なこと話せたら
If I can put my true feelings into words and talk about what's important,
今日もリスタート
I'll restart today again.
どんなに君だから 口に出して言わなければ
No matter how dense you are, if I don't say it out loud,
今君に伝えるよ ねえ、好きです
I'll tell you now. Hey, I love you.
世界は恋に落ちている 光の矢胸を射す
The world is falling in love, an arrow of light piercing my chest,
全部わかりたいんだよ ねえ、聞かせて
I want to understand everything, hey, let me hear it.
手繰り寄せて もう0センチ
Reeling you in to zero centimeters.
駆け抜けた日々々に 忘れられない 忘れられない
In the days we ran through, I can't forget, I can't forget
忘れない 忘られない 輝く1ページ
I won't forget this shining page.
はーい、ということで
Haai, so up to here,
ここまではあきさまとロボ子さんと一緒に歌わせていただきました
Aki-sama and Roboco-san and I sang together!
みんなありがとー！
Thank you everyone!
さてさて、ここからはなんと、重大発表が2つありまーす！
Now then, from here, we have two major announcements!
まず1つ目が、こちら、じゃーん！
First is this, ta-da!
癒月ちょこ 誕生日記念2026
[Visual: Yuzuki Choco Birthday Commemoration 2026]
それではちょっと詳しくご紹介していきたいと思います
Now I'd like to introduce them in detail.
まずは、こちら、ちょこのクッション！
First, this! Choco's cushion!
いやこれね、ちょこの誕生日といえば毎年ナルダック先生ありがとうございますということで
You know, speaking of Choco's birthday every year, thank you Nardack-sensei, so
今年もナルダック先生にめちゃめちゃ素敵なイラスト描き下ろしていただきました！
this year too, Nardack-sensei drew an amazingly wonderful illustration for us!
今回のテーマはバレンタインということで
The theme this time is Valentine's Day,
ちょっとね、チョコメイトと抱きながら、ちょっと今回はチョコレート風のクッションにしてみました！
so hugging my Choco-mates, this time we made it into a chocolate-styled cushion!
かわいいでしょ？
Isn't it cute?
サイズ感がちょうど枕くらいになってるので、ちょっとねおヒルネの時とか仮眠用にすやっとできる感じで使えちゃいます！
The size is just right like a pillow, so you can use it for taking a nap or resting comfortably!
なんと
And guess what?
今回初めてちょっとね お菓子が作れる
For the very first time, we're able to make our own treats—
なんとなんと、ちょこのチョコレート型！
None other than... Choco's chocolate mold!
耐熱も、冷却も、あったかいのも、冷たいのも両方使えちゃって
It can handle both heat and cold, whether you want something warm or cold!
ちょっとね、チョコレートと、チョコメイトの、今回はチョコレート型になっております！
So yeah, this time it's shaped like chocolate and Chocomeates—into a chocolate mold!
ま、マフィンとかね、クッキーとか、あとはまあ普通に冷やし固めてチョコレート入れたりとか、なんか色々使えるからぜひみんなも作ってみてね！
Like, for muffins, cookies, or just chilling chocolate inside it—you can use it for so many things, so definitely give it a try, everyone!
そして続いてはこちら、お待たせしました！ちょこのすやすやぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
And next up is this—thanks for waiting! Choco's Sleepy Stuffed Toy Keychain!
ま、チョコといえばね、睡眠ということで、超ロングスリーパーのちょこが、今回はぬいぐるみキーホルダーとなって、ちょっとすやすやぬいぐるみで、作らせていただきました！
Since Choco is all about sleep, as a super long sleeper, Choco turned into a sleepy stuffed toy keychain this time, so we had it made into a sleepy plushie!
ま、ずっとね、肌身離さず持ってれば、いつかあ、がって聞こえてくるかもしれない！
If you keep it close to you all the time, maybe one day... you'll hear it screaming!
そして今年もございます、癒月ちょこガチ下ろし台本の、耳舐めASMR台本！
And we also have this year—Yuzuki Choco's newly written script, an ear-licking ASMR script!
取りましたよ、ちょこのASMRボイス！今回ね、耳舐めのほうは、3つございます！
We've recorded them, Choco's ASMR voices! This time, there are three ear-licking tracks!
1つ目が、溶けかけのチョコレート。
The first one is "Melting Chocolate."
いや、こちらはね、あの、皆様がご想像しているより、ちょっと、あの、えちちかもしれないんですけど、まあ配信ではね、絶対にできないボイスとなっておりますので、是非ともね、皆様ご購入して聴いてみてください！
Now, this one might be a bit more lewd than you're all imagining, but since it's a voice you can absolutely never do on stream, definitely make sure to purchase and listen to it, everyone!
そしてもう1つが、残業後のご褒美デザート、ということで、こちらはね、ちょことの同棲シチュエーションとなっております！
And the second one is "Reward Dessert After Overtime", which is a co-living situation with Choco!
はい、ちょこが残業してきて、帰ってきたときの、うーん、ま、旦那様は、ちょこなのか？君なのか？どっちなんだろうね？まあ、ちょっと聴いてみてよ！
Yes, when Choco comes back after working overtime... hmm, are you the husband, or is Choco? Which one is it? Well, just give it a listen!
そしてそして、年下の幼馴染みの、ツンデレバレンタイン、ということで、今回は聴いている君たちが、ちょっと隣りのお兄ちゃんになった気分で聴いてみてください！こちらもおね、耳舐めボイスとなっておりますが、なんとこちら、どMの方は絶対に聴いていただけたら、ちょっとニソニソしちゃうんじゃないかなって思います！
And finally, "Tsundere Valentine with a Younger Childhood Friend", so this time, please listen to it feeling like you've become the older brother next door! This is also an ear-licking voice, but if any extreme masochists listen to this, I think you'll be grinning from ear to ear!
フルセットご購入の方、フルセット特典、今回はなんと初めてチェキ風ブロマイドカードになりました！
For those who purchase the full set, as a full-card bonus, for the first time ever it's become a Cheki-style bromide card!
ちょっとこちらね、数量限定で直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージが入っております！
This one comes with an autograph and foil-stamped duplicate message in limited quantities!
通常版は箔押し複製サインと複製メッセージが入ります！そしてね、特典がもう1つ、フルセット購入特典として、
The regular version includes a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message! And as another bonus for purchasing the full set,
焼きモチのじゅーっとASMRボイスが入っております！いや、こちらはね、ちょっとあの、甘々のじゅーボイスなので、普段まちょこ嫉妬しないんですけど、ちょっとまあ、何に嫉妬してるかは聴いてからのお楽しみなんですが、ぜひぜひ、ニヤニヤしながら聴いておいてください！ぜひ手に入れてください！
It includes a "Jealousy Sizzling ASMR Voice"! Now, this is a super sweet sizzling voice, so normally Choco doesn't get jealous, but what she's jealous of is a surprise for after you listen, so definitely listen while grinning ear to ear! Make sure to get your hands on it!
そしてそして、1台告知、2つ目は、こちらー！
And now, for the first major announcement—the second one is this!
…ねぇ、ちょこた…もう二度と会えないの？
"...Hey, Choco... can we never meet again?"
不思議ね。キミの言葉を聞くと、なんだか元気が出てきちゃう。
It's strange. Hearing your words somehow gives me energy.
ちょこが小悪魔なんて……
Choco, a little devil...
もう一度、会いたいよ。
I want to see you once more.
大好きになってほしい
I want you to love me.
ねぇ、もしよければキミに……ちょこの思い出話、聞いてほしいの。
Hey, if you don't mind... I want you to listen to Choco's memories.
「The Beginning」 12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリース＆連動ボイスドラマプロジェクトスタート
"The Beginning" - 12-Month Consecutive Original Song Release & Linked Voice Drama Project Start!
3/15から毎月15日0時オリジナル楽曲リリース
Original song release every month on the 15th at midnight starting March 15th!
豪華アーティスト参加
Featuring luxurious artists!
癒月ちょこ あなたのストーリーを辿った 全12話のボイスドラマ
A 12-episode voice drama following the story of Yuzuki Choco and you!
「The Beginning」project 始動！
The "The Beginning" project begins!
はーい、というわけで、癒月ちょこ、12ヶ月連続オリジナル楽曲リリースが決定しました！
And so, Yuzuki Choco's 12-month consecutive original song release has been decided!
ねぇ〜
Hey~
しかもこちら、なんとなんと
And what's more, believe it or not...
オリ曲にストーリー連動のボイスドラマが
original songs and a synchronized story voice drama
一緒にリリースされます！
will be released together!
いや、こちらね、約1話から12話まで
From episodes 1 to 12,
1曲ずつに連動して、ボイスドラマもあるので、ぜひぜひ楽しみに待っててください！
each paired with a song, there'll also be a voice drama, so please look forward to it!
そして、今回はね、その記念すべき1曲目をこれから披露したいと思います！
And now, I'm going to perform the very first, commemorative song for you!
まだ戻れないから
Because I still can't go back,
また愛しさが勝るキミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you again where my love for you grows stronger.
キミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you...
キミの秒針
Your second hand,
キミから受け取った壊れそうなストーリー
A fragile story I received from you,
どこまでも広がる青い空
spreading endlessly into the blue sky.
変わらない毎日も色のない夢も
Unchanging days and colorless dreams,
手放して始めようよ
let's let go of them and begin!
不安の夜を数え 泣きながら迎えた
Counting nights of anxiety, welcoming mornings with tears—
朝でもいい
even that is fine.
時計の針のように刻んだ思い出たち広げた
Spreading out the memories carved like the hands of a clock—
どこでもないからまた
Since it's nowhere else, once more
愛しさが勝るキミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you where my love for you grows stronger.
ふたりで温めた大切なストーリー
The precious story we warmed together,
ここまで続いた果てしない道
a never-ending path that continued so far.
疲れたら変わるからそう言ってくれた
You told me, "If you get tired, things will change,"
優しさに触れられた
and I was touched by your kindness.
受け入れてくれたこと忘れない
I won't forget that you accepted me.
嬉しくて泣いた日々さえ
Even the days I cried with happiness...
雨上がるの胸に刻んだ文字のように綺麗なキミだから
Like letters carved into my chest as the rain clears up, you are so pure and beautiful,
キミだから もっとのことか一つ一つが
Because it's you, every single thing...
今も 宝物なの
is still a treasure to this day.
支えてくれたから
Because you supported me,
輝けるこの気持ち届けよう
let's deliver this shining feeling!
時計の針のように
Like the hands of a clock,
刻んだ思い出たち広がれた
the memories we carved have spread out...
どこでもないからまた愛しさが勝る
Since it's nowhere else, once more my love grows stronger—
キミに逢いたいよ
I want to see you!
雨上がるの胸に
Into my chest as the rain clears,
刻んだ文字のように綺麗だ
shining like the carved letters—
キミだからもっとのことか一つ一つが今も宝物なの
Because it's you, every single thing is still a treasure.
はーい、ということで、
All right, so,
みんなどうだったかな？
how did everyone like it?
今回の新曲、キミの秒針は、
My new song, "Kimi no Byoushin,"
紫道のマオ様が作詞、
features lyrics by Shido Mao-sama,
そして、みめぐみあき様が作編曲、
and composition and arrangement by Mimegumi Aki-sama.
そして編曲にはなんと、加藤タカユキ様も加わっていただきました！
And for the arrangement, amazingly, Kato Takayuki-sama also joined in!
いやー今回は、ボイスドラマ連動企画の第1弾として、
Man, this time, as the first part of our voice drama tie-in project,
ストーリー全体のね、テーマソングを担うような、カッコイイ楽曲に仕上がっております！
it's shaped up into a cool song that carries the theme song of the whole story!
まあ、ドラマの鍵となるね、秒針というメタファーにもよう注目してください！
Well, please pay close attention to the metaphor of the "second hand," which becomes the key to the drama!
紫道さんだけではなく、この後ね、豪華アーティストの皆様にも、たくさん参加いただいたので、皆様リリースをお楽しみに！
Not just Shido-san, but afterwards, lots of gorgeous artists will be participating too, so everyone look forward to the release!
こちらのキミの秒針は、
This "Kimi no Byoushin,"
各音楽サイトは、ちょっと間が空いちゃうんだけど、3月15日の0時から配信予定でございます！
will be available on various music streaming sites starting March 15th at midnight, though there's a bit of a wait!
ま、ちょっとね公開まで時間が空くから、それまでこの配信、何度も見返してきてください、聴き込んでね！
Well, since there's time until release, please rewatch this stream as many times as you like, and listen closely to it!
そしてそして、MVもね、ちょっと後日公開なので、楽しみにしててくださーい！
And also, the MV will be released at a later date, so please look forward to that!
ということで、
With that said,
今日のちょこの生誕ライブはどうだったかな？
how was Choco's birthday live today?
ま、このあとはすぐに、ちょっとね、ボト、最初のほうでごお披露目した、
Well, right after this, um, well, we announced it at the beginning,
のえちゃんラミたんとの3人の初恋大戦争のMV公開があって、
the MV release of Noe-chan, Rami-tan, and my "First Love Great War" trio song,
そのあと、メンゲンで、ちょっとライブと、撮影会の続きとか、
and after that, for members only, we'll have more of the live, the photoshoot continuation,
ちょっとね、メンゲンでしか見れないシチュエーションドラマとかやるので、
and situational dramas that you can only see for members,
ぜひぜひ、気になる人は見に行ってください！
so definitely check it out if you're interested!
それではまたあとでお会いしましょう！
Well then, let's meet again later!
お疲れーと！
Good work!